module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'When was the first gay and lesbian march on Washington?', 
    a: '1990',
    b: '1985',
    c: '1981',
    d: '1965',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year did the APA remove homosexuality from its list of mental disorders?', 
    a: '1971',
    b: '1973',
    c: '1977',
    d: '1980',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many stripes does the Rainbow Flag currenlty have?', 
    a: '8',
    b: '7',
    c: '6',
    d: '5',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which New England state was the first to make gay marriage legal?', 
    a: 'Massachussets',
    b: 'Connecticut',
    c: 'New Hampshire',
    d: 'Vermont',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What gay African-American author\'s works include "The Fire Next Time" & "Sonny\'s Blues"?' , 
    a: 'James Baldwin',
    b: 'Barbara Smith',
    c: 'Essex Hemphill',
    d: 'Sapphire',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What US state was the first to decriminalize homosexuality?', 
    a: 'California',
    b: 'Illinois',
    c: 'New York',
    d: 'Ohio',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What country was the first in the world to legalize gay marriage?', 
    a: 'France',
    b: 'Denmark',
    c: 'The Netherlands',
    d: 'Spain',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What US state was the first to outlaw discrimination based on sexual orientation?', 
    a: 'New York',
    b: 'Colorado',
    c: 'Wisconsin',
    d: 'Minnesota',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What famous gay rights activist was murdered by the San Francisco City Supervisor, Dan White?', 
    a: 'Matthew Shephard',
    b: 'Tennessee Williams',
    c: 'Dick Button',
    d: 'Harvey Milk',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'When was the first gay pride parade held in the US?', 
    a: '1968',
    b: '1969',
    c: '1970',
    d: '1971',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];